I wish I had superpowers,
so I could stop the world.
Because what matters to me
is the two of us.
We have each other anyway.
If you're not ready to face the world yet,
we can run away from it.
Starting today,
Mikoy is now considered
an enemy of the state.
This is basically a shoot-to-kill order
in the eyes of covert operators.
Mikoy, didn't I tell you?
You can't take a different route.
We have to stick to the same routine.
Otherwise, you'll stand out.
I just had to stop somewhere earlier.
You have no idea how happy I am.
Do you know where our child is?
Maybe she's already in Cebu
with our future in-laws.
Clearly, they know something
about what's going on.
Then, let's reach out to them
more aggressively.
Let's send a grand emissary.
Oh, wow!
Looking sharp!
Is it your JS Prom?
You look old.
Do you know these two?
Hold on, bro. It's blurry.
I cannot see it.
I'll give you some money
to get your eyes checked.
Hold on. Let me call my friends.
It'll be easier to see.
BARANGAY POLICE
Someone's looking for brother Mikoy.
Lookouts!
He's looking for Mikoy.
Why are you looking for Mikoy?
I got nothing,
but a hospital bill for our man.
You know what, Bok?
What Sir Norberto
was trying to say is right.
With all of Mikoy's knowledge
about the agency's secrets,
I won't be surprised if he becomes
the enemy of the state
in the eyes of the higher-ups.
Of course, it will be that way.
I won't be surprised if he
is taken down by the law operatives
because he's considered a traitor now.
We're already there.
But do you really think
Mikoy would betray us?
Looks like our guy
was simply blinded by love.
That's why he ran away with Chiara.
Whatever Mikoy's reason may be,
we need to find him immediately.
You're right.
The warrant of arrest
is enough to be tantamount
to a shoot-to-kill order.
No matter how immoral and illegal it is.
Thank you.
Thank you, Bok, for supporting me.
I mean,
General Norberto is right.
You're the one who had
the most doubts about Mikoy.
But even so,
you still believe that we need
to find and save him.
Well.
Who else would support you here?
It's just me.
There's only one place where
I think they know where Mikoy is.
How could they not know each other when
they've been connected since childhood?
They've joined forces
since they were young.
They're godfathers, godmothers,
and compadres.
That's how it is in the Philippines.
That's how Filipinos are.
They're scrutinizing outsiders.
And La Morte Bianca
wants us to stay quiet for now.
The solution is simple.
Let's show up there ourselves,
reach out, and make an appearance,
show them we're being genuine.
Come to think of it,
why has Agent Sianong
been so supportive recently?
Back then, when it came to Mikoy,
he was like a constant devil's advocate.
Dara, can't you see?
So much chaos has already happened
in this office, in our agency.
Now is the time when we need unity.
That unity talk is nonsense.
No one believes that anymore.
Just admit it.
You have hidden feelings.
Hey!
Cut it out.
Dara, take her back to the hospital.
You can't order me around.
And I won't let the person
I love disappear again.
"And I won't let the person
I love disappear again."
Then he walks out.
Why?
It's true.
I love Agent Alex.
I love you, too.
Rafa, Kian, and General Norberto too.
I love everyone in this office.
I'm just a loving person.
Tell that to your grandmother.
For a covert government agent,
you're not very good at lying.
Hey, Agent Sianong.
I've watched so many K-dramas.
I practically have
a doctoral degree majoring
in second lead syndrome.
That's why I know that deep inside,
you really think it's better
if Mikoy is out of the picture.
If it's your choice,
maybe it'd be better
if he was never found.
You know, if you were a Fishbook ad,
I wouldn't even wait three seconds,
let alone five,
I'd skip you right away.
You talk too much.
You're so defensive!
You know, it's a good thing
Madam gave us permission.
Even though it's not our day off yet.
Maybe she's happy with us.
Maybe.
Wait. Are you hungry, sweetheart?
Yes, let's eat!
Let's go.
Ouch!
You go ahead.
- No.
- It's okay.
Don't cry. We're going to get ice cream.
Hey.
You.
They just look so happy.
Why?
Do you want that, too?
I do, but…
Why is there a but?
It just feels impossible.
Come on, sweetheart.
Always remember this, okay?
Everything is possible.
Oh, you.
Look at it.
We're here in Hong Kong together.
Can you imagine that?
Our relationship survived,
despite all the secrets and pretending.
Because our love is real.
That's why to me, no matter what happens,
there's always a tomorrow waiting for us.
And I'm so excited for our future.
I can face any tomorrow
as long as you're with me.
That's it!
That's the spirit, sweetheart!
That's why I love you.
Is it because I look like
the ultimate leading man?
And because you make me believe in things
that even I struggle to believe.
More, Angge.
Easy now. It's hot.
We don't want it burned.
Okay.
You should put it there.
Tess.
We have visitors.
Here, put this in a box.
Careful, it's hot.
Okay.
Angelito, where are the drinks?
- Mom!
- The--
- There it is!
- Coming right up.
Thank you very much!
Bechay, come here and hold this.
Okay.
Take care, Betch.
Chief!
- Let's drink later.
- Hi, Miss Tess!
- Hello. Would you like some torta?
- Hello. Good afternoon.
Go ahead and eat.
- There.
- Thank you, ma'am.
- Here.
- Thank you.
Oh no, this is enough, really.
You need something to wash
it down with when you're eating.
- Right?
- True.
And so people will know
that you're our customers.
- Right?
- Yes.
That's right.
Why do people need to see
that we're your customers?
Is there a problem?
Oh dear, this stays between us, okay?
But our folks here are on heightened alert
because there are
so many people lurking around.
We don't like outsiders.
Of course, you know there are a lot
of land grabbers, family snatchers,
dog grabbers, cat grabbers.
Right?
They're there! Come on. Say hi!
See?
Of course, I wouldn't want you
to get beaten up
because you're outsiders.
But I know you're close to Mikoy, right?
All right, go ahead and eat.
I still have a lot to do.
Come on, Bechay.
- Thank you.
- Enjoy your meal.
Sir, we both know why you're stressed.
And it's not because of your phone.
I can't stop worrying.
And I know she talked to you
before she disappeared.
And for some reason,
she trusts you.
What do I need to know?
Honey!
Honey, hurry!
- Honey.
- Why?
Is it an emergency? I'll get my gun.
Why would we need a gun?
And why are we whispering?
Because I think the G.A.G.O.
still haven't stopped looking
for Mikoy and Chiara.
What is it, Bok?
Do you really think Mikoy is here?
Because we might not be able
to handle the backlash.
They won't do anything to us
if we talk to them properly.
And there's only one way to find out
if Mikoy and Chiara are really here.
There you go again, Bok.
I was the last person La Fornarina
spoke to before she disappeared.
Along with Mikoy.
Where did they go?
Let me do the talking.
I'll do the talking.
I want everything to come from me.
- Wait. Hold it!
- Hold it.
- Hold it!
- Hey, hey, hey!
You can't!
- Stay here.
- No, no!
- No!
- Sir, are you sure?
I'll finish you off.
- That's a bit much.
- Chief, let it go.
Let it slide.
How may I help you?
To be honest, just like Mikoy,
we don't want you getting involved
in all this trouble.
But you flew to Cebu,
to come all the way here.
That already involves us.
Because I'm desperate.
So we had no choice
but to come here and talk to you.
What for?
"The above-named individual
is under active pursuit
and is considered armed
and highly dangerous
and capable of violent resistance.
All enforcement units are…
directed to… and arrest…"
But we can still keep Mikoy
from getting hurt if you help us.
You know, I…
I'm sorry, Agent Alex,
but we don't know where Mikoy is.
Mr. Mario.
We wouldn't have come
all the way here if we thought
you didn't know where Mikoy is.
And like you, we only want
what's best for Mikoy's safety--
Nonsense!
You were the ones who approached him first
to make him part of your mission.
You promised him protection.
And now you're saying
his safety is your priority.
Do you think we sleep well at night?
The answer is no.
Not because every minute
we're thinking about Mikoy's condition.
We don't know where Mikoy is,
what he's doing,
or whether he's with Chiara.
So it's best
if you leave.
And don't drag my family into this.
You heard what Mr. Mario said.
- Leave!
- Go.
- Go on. Leave!
- Leave this place!
Come on.
- Go on. Leave!
- Let's go.
- Leave now!
There!
All right, thank you.
Maybe we just came at the wrong time, Bok.
Bok.
Let's try again another day.
Let's give them time to trust us more.
Bok.
Maybe it's about time to give up on Mikoy.
Out of more than 190 countries,
they had over 190 options.
Each country has different
security levels and policies.
That means
they're left with fewer than 30 countries
that are easier options.
And if you're going to take
into consideration
that I made Philippine passports for them,
their options are further limited.
But don't worry.
Of course, to help them
move around safely,
I made sure all their documents
were in order.
Not just passports,
but with supporting documents
and character descriptions.
And sir, don't worry.
Your daughter, Chiara, is smart.
She knows exactly what to do
in situations like this.
And Mikoy is incredibly resourceful.
That's why they make such a perfect team.
Come on.
You know, sir, believe it or not,
in this story,
I'm Team MikChi.
Sweetheart, what are you thinking about?
I thought you were a world-class assassin.
That you can figure out
your target with just one look.
And now you can't read me?
What I'm reading is
that you're deeply in love with me.
There!
Exactly!
Do you miss your mom and dad?
Angelito?
The simple bakery of Pinagpala.
You know, I don't think
I can hide anything from you anymore.
You know me too well.
You know, sweetheart, you're like rain.
I'm completely soaked by you.
Sweetheart, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry that I'm the reason
you're far away from your family.
Come on, sweetheart. Don't apologize.
I'm sure they understand
my decision, okay?
They know that even if I'm far away,
I'm still happy because I'm with you.
Isn't that what really matters in life?
That I'm happy with the decisions
and the life I've chosen.
And let's just keep it under
the name Chiara Valtrovi.
- Okay?
- Oh, please!
- You, honestly!
- Why?
You're so good with sweet, charming words.
But just make sure
you only use those moves on me!
If I find out you're being sweet
to someone else,
your eyes will be
the only thing without bruises!
Come on, sweetheart.
I don't know whether
to feel flattered or scared.
But I'm sorry, sweetheart.
I guess I'm just getting used
to this kind of life again.
When I was in Prague, at least,
I knew I could still go home.
But now,
I'm not even sure
if I'll ever see them again.
I promise you.
Even if we're far away right now,
living in hiding,
that doesn't mean
you'll never see your family again.
You can look forward to the day
when we'll all be one normal family.
And we'll be together
with the people we love.
You can count on that.
Agent Alex, I have an update.
Wasn't there an order for us
to monitor Viktor Valtrovi?
So he's going to see Chiara?
So I immediately obtained
his flight information.
- Prague?
- No.
Sicily?
Not there either.
- Then, where?
- Where?
The Queen City of the South.
Cebu City.
Lookouts!
Sir Mario!
Sir Mario, a car just arrived.
Bechay, Angelito, go upstairs.
We miss you all very much!
Viktor's here to fish
for information from the Pinagpala's.
Or Viktor came to give them information.
Either way, we don't have access
to that information.
It's either from Mario or Viktor.
I know how to get information
from their family.
Are you going to tell that to Agent Alex?
Wait, then she's going to find Mikoy.
How about your love team?
Sweetheart, are you okay?
- I can't calm down.
- Is there a problem?
I got a bad feeling a while ago.
I thought someone was following me.
- Why? What happened?
- Go on. Get dressed. Hurry!
Wait, what's happening?
We're running out of time.
We have to go now!
They've found us!